So, at the popular request of the working masses, measurement the classic way.
We'll measure with these resistors here, identical, 33 ohms each.
So, the coil is in the system.
Here are two wires.
This is the output from the grenade.
These two wires here, this is the inductor.
Here we have the common point, the black wire, ground for the oscilloscope.
Right here is where the ground is hooked up.
Here is the generator's ground.
The capacitance hasn't changed.
The same half volt amplitude.
So, right now we've hooked up the 33 ohm resistor to the generator output.
Here we look at the wire from the generator.
This terminal arrives at the common point.
This goes through a diode to the 33 ohms.
Let's see.
This is our current.
Remember, 12 divisions.
Now we switch the output of the analog ammeter also to 33 ohms to the grenade output.
We've hooked it up and we connect the generator to the grenade inductor.
Let's see.
Our current came out to 20 divisions.
In the picture, we have the blue trace.
This is from the signal generator.
It is hooked up, the probe with the blue ring, to the output of the signal generator that goes to the inductor.
The yellow trace is sitting on the output from the grenade in parallel with the capacitance.
We do the measurement on the analog ammeter through a resistor.
Here, look, now I'll switch to before the resistor.
Our current came out to 20 divisions.
And after the resistor, our current came out to just under 20 divisions.
To the theorists, show me an LC resonance where both current and voltage grow.
And here are the frequency beats.